{
    "id": "ee3fd79439454e908b4a169440a6070f",
    "title": "Sentence Completion Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His ideas are little different ……………………….. those of his father.",
            "description": "We generally use from after different.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "of",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The new job isn’t ……………………….. different from the old one.",
            "description": "Different can be modified by little, any or not much. Many is not possible.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This fragrance is ………………………….. different from that.",
            "description": "Different can be modified by little. It cannot be modified by few.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………………. older than his wife.",
            "description": "We cannot use very to modify comparatives.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Do you know Orwell’s books?’ ‘I haven’t read ……………………….’",
            "description": "In negative sentences we use any.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "none"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Economists doubt ……………………… prices will fall.",
            "description": "We can use whether, if or that to introduce clauses after doubt.",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "that",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "She was dressed ……………………….. a purple gown.",
            "description": "The preposition in is used in this expression.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. her illness, she could not attend the conference.",
            "description": "Due to and owing to can both mean because of.",
            "answers": [
                "Owing to",
                "Due to",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was in Mumbai ………………………… three weeks.",
            "description": "We use for to indicate duration.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop was closed ……………………….. the whole of May.",
            "description": "We use during to talk about the whole of a period.",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "in",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Come up and see me ....................................",
            "description": "We use sometime or one day to refer to an indefinite time in the future. ",
            "answers": [
                "once",
                "sometime",
                "one day"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "One of my friends ........................................ a scientist.",
            "description": "After one of, the verb is singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}